ghafla.com 2015-06-09

# Uncategorised - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

Details
     Category: [Uncategorised](http://www.ghafla.co.ke/privacy-policy/2-uncategorised)
     Created on Monday, 15 October 2012 11:47 
     Hits: 31879 

We are committed to protecting user privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices in relation to the collection, use, and storage of information that you may provide via this Website at www.ghafla.co.ke (hereinafter referred to as "Website"). Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information to this Website.

In this Privacy Policy a reference to "Ghafla" or "we" or "us" or "our" means the Ghafla! Inc, the owner of the Website.  
 **Your Consent**

By using this Website, and/or by clicking 'I Accept' to the terms and conditions when becoming a member of Ghafla you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions and this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Website you consent to the collection, use, disclosure and storage of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use the Ghafla service after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on the Ghafla Website, you are consenting to the changes.  
 **Information Management**

Like many Websites, this Website collects information from its visitors both by permitting you to establish user accounts and to communicate directly with us and other users of the Website via e-mail, group discussions, private messaging and feedback forms etc. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information including sensitive information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on).

Some areas of this Website may require you to submit information to enable you to benefit from the special features (such as groups, events, updates, private messaging) or to participate in a particular activity (such as an event or promotion). You consent to us using the information you have submitted to contact you in relation to those special features and activities and to administer your participation in those activities.

Any information posted on group or personal discussion forums may become public information. While we strive to protect and respect your privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose in a bulletin board or discussion forum.  
 **Passive Information Collection**

We may use cookies to assign your computer a User ID so that we can identify your computer on our server. This enables us to track your use of the Website and to learn about your preferences so that we can make our Website better. In most cases, you may configure your web browser to disable cookies. We do not use cookies to collect and store personal information about you.  
 **Transaction Information**

Ghafla cannot accept your order until you have paid for it in full. You may pay by Visa, EuroCard or MasterCard, (only a credit card may be used).

Upon payment, Ghafla will confirm receipt of your order by an acknowledgement displayed onscreen once your payment details have been accepted, followed by an e-mail which will be sent to the e-mail address you provide on your order details.

You will have an opportunity to check and correct any input errors in your order up until the point at which you submit your order by clicking the “confirm order” button on the checkout page.

Ghafla reserves the right to choose not to accept your order for any reason, at its discretion, and will not be liable to you or anyone else in those circumstances.

The prices for services offered on this website are as set out on the website. All prices are in euros (€), inclusive of VAT.

In the unlikely event that the price of a service has been incorrectly advertised on this website, we will contact you by e-mail (at the address provided with your order details) or telephone you, to ask whether you wish to proceed with the order at the correct price. If you are not happy to proceed, or we are unable to obtain your instructions, we will cancel the order and provide you with a full refund of any monies debited.

By using a credit card to pay for your order, you confirm that the card being used is yours. All credit card holders are subject to validation checks and authorization by the card issuer. If the issuer of your card refuses to authorize payment, we will not accept your order and we will not be liable for any delay and we are not obliged to inform you of the reason for the refusal. We are not responsible for your card issuer or bank charging you as a result of our processing of your credit card payment in accordance with your order.

When you pay the monthly fee or for using any other services provided by Ghafla, we ask you to provide information related to each transaction, consisting of your full name, contact information (address, phone number, email), the amount of the transaction, and the type of the credit card you use for the transaction and the verification code of your card. We retain this information for each of your transactions through Ghafla and may add this information to your account profile to be used for future transactions that you may make with us. We also collect the Internet address (IP address) and other identifying information about the computer or device you use to access your Ghafla account, in order to help detect possible instances of unauthorized transactions.

In the unlikely event of fraudulent or unauthorized use of your payment card by someone else to purchase goods from us on our server we will refund to you any money received by us as a result but only if you have notified your payment card issuer and us by emailing us on [info@Ghafla.com](mailto:support@humanipo.com) as soon as you became aware of the unauthorized use of your card.

We recommend that you do not communicate your payment card details to anyone, including us, by e-mail. We cannot be responsible for any losses you may incur in transmitting information to us by internet link or by e-mail. Any such loss shall not be borne either wholly or partly by us, and shall be entirely your responsibility.

If you have any additional queries about security, please e-mail: [info@Ghafla.com](mailto:support@humanipo.com)  
 **Use and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise stated, we may use your information to improve the Website, and to communicate information to you, and for our marketing, promotional, and research purposes. We may also use your personal information for purposes related to your membership of this Website, which would be reasonably expected by you. We will not disclose information that personally identifies you to advertisers. However, we may use your personal information to provide advertisers with aggregate statistics of people who have seen their advertisements on the Website.

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to our related bodies corporate, advisers or consultants including third parties who provide us with administrative services that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition, you agree that we may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties, located in European union and/or any other country, but only (i) to third parties we use to support our business, in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; (ii) in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of the business of this Website to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such third party to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy; or (iii) where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations.

If you opt in at the point of registration, you acknowledge and agree that our commercial sponsors, business partners or associates located within European Union and overseas, may use the Website to offer you information, provide you with details about events and organizations, or for other commercial purposes which your user profile indicates that you may be interested in.

If you subsequently decide that you do not wish to receive information either from us or third parties associated with us, please contact us with your request to be removed from the relevant mailing list. We will use reasonable endeavours to remove your name within 7 days of receipt of notice.

In addition, we will make full use of all information acquired through this Website that is not in personally identifiable form.

Under no circumstances will we sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.  
 **Security and Transborder data flow**

We take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your computer to our Website and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, use, modification, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

However, you should keep in mind that the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this Website may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username and passwords and any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are using the Internet. Please contact us if you become aware or have reason to believe that there has been any unauthorized use of your personal information in connection with this Website.

Personal data may be transferred outside European Union, but will remain subject to principles for fair handling of the information which are substantially similar to those used in European union and will not be collected, held, used or disclosed by the recipients of the information in a manner inconsistent with this policy.  
 **Links to Other Websites**

This Website may contain links or references to other Websites. Please be aware that we do not control other Websites and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those Websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every Website you visit.  
 **Disclaimer**

We will only collect, use or disclose information that personally identifies you in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless we are required to disclose it by law or in our opinion we are required by disclose it to protect the rights or property of us or any third party, or to avoid injury to any person. ****
